Hello everybody welcome to Step Up Live today's
video I will tell you how
you have to do your car insurance and
what things you have to keep in mind if
you want to buy your car insurance step
by step process we will tell you completely
which is the best car insurance
ICC Lombard of 2022 we will
give you all the information about it if your car
insurance is given or it has expired
then definitely watch this video till the end
you will get the link in the description
check the entire process and
definitely get it done because this is a legal
complication if your car gets into an
accident and the other person gets
damaged then it becomes
very important for you to quickly get
these details of today's video which
told you about ICC Lombard which has been a channel
insurance super brand in 2022
we have given you its link in the description
if you click then
you will reach a dashboard like this first of all
you have to enter your vehicle number which is your
registration mobile number an email
address and gate  You will have to click on N Court.
After ticking both the places,
after doing this you will get an OTP and
after entering the OTP, an interface like this will appear
on your screen. If you see, the
details of your vehicle will automatically
start appearing on the screen
because
they have already picked up the vehicle number from the registration.
Here you will see
three basic plans on the screen. The first one is No
Frills, the second one is Zero Depression and
Smart Plan. They will tell you the information of these three plans.
One more thing is that if
your credit score is good then you can
also get an extra discount.
If you look at the check eligibility option on the
screen, you will see it
on the right hand side top and from there you
can definitely try it by checking your credit score. If you want Quicklime then
which of these plans should you select
and what are the details of all the three plans, the
first plan is No Frills
Just Basic Plan which will do your basic
insurance, that is, if you meet with any
accident on the road then
any damage to your car will be covered.  This insurance will not cover the
damages to the other person's car, but it is not for you. If
you see, Roadside Assistant, Car Damages
and Standard Personal Accident Tax, all
three are covered. You
can add or remove them if you want. Your
prices will also vary accordingly. Most
importantly, this is not a recommended plan
because the Zero Depression Plan, if you
look at it carefully, your car's
damages will also be covered there. So,
for you, you are protected against your car
value depression. That is, Roadside
Assistant, Zero Appreciation Consumable Tax, Car Damages
and Standard Personal
Protection Accident Tax. All these things are there, so
I would comment on this, you should definitely consider the second one. The
third one is a
smart plan which is being launched based on your switch.
It has 7 benefits,
such as protection against
loss of personal belongings and other things.
If this is your driving
relief or you  If you don't make a claim,
you can also get a discount for the next air
from Incline. So you can definitely
think about this plan is well
moving on personal protection. The policy is
around ₹325, which is giving coverage of ₹3 lakh.
If you want, you can remove it
or add it based on it. If you
already have a good life insurance or
health insurance, then you
can remove it moving on to the next plan.
Think once you pay the bill to the next step.
From the first of January 2023, KYC
authentication has been made mandatory for
insurance policies. So, if you had
bought without KYC earlier, then that would have been possible,
but it will not be possible now. If you
look here, you will be
shown the option to begin your KYC process here.
You have seen all three plans so far. Whatever
plans you have seen, which we have shown you all three, out of
these, the most recommended one is the zero
depression plan of
13941, which is showing, at this time, this is a very
good plan for you.  GST will be added and
you will see it. Let's move ahead quickly.
If you
go to do KYC from here,
you will see three options related to PAN card,
Aadhar card and CKYC. If
you want to do it with PAN card, then that too will be done
easily. After this, you will have to
confirm your policy. You will have to enter the third policy
which is your policy information. You will have to
fill in the nominee details and
proceed to pay. Another thing you should keep in
mind is the
depreciation cost of your car, according to that,
you should definitely keep
your policy in mind, because it is important that
you get yourself a safe insurance by
taking advantage of all these insurances because car is such a thing which can become a
liability for you and your
family if you have a major
accident or there is a situation of getting any repair done.
So, if you
liked this video, if you want to
see more such videos related to
finance  And growth definitely subscribe to the
channel link of ICC Lombard, you will
get it in the description, you
definitely check it and compare it as per your convenience,
I have told you all the benefits of these three
policies, so that you
can take a decision as per your convenience and apply, and do not miss
this date on insurance because it can be a big
problem, if the
police catches you without
insurance or you have an accident and you do
not have insurance, then it can be a big
problem, so definitely check it,
ICC Longway Trusted Partner, so
definitely it is worth watching, thank you, so
match and bye bye